goodix.com 2015-12-26

# 

Privacy Policy 

The following information describes how Huiding would collect and use your personal information to provide services that you request or when you choose to provide us with your personal information. 

Information Collection 

Huiding fully respects your privacy, and shall spare no effort to protect your personal information. Generally, you will not be required to provide any personal information for browsing this Website. 

In order to measure the effectiveness of our online presence, some pages on this Website may use cookies, which are small text files that a site transfers to a user’s (visitor’s) hard disk or browser for added functionality or for tracking site usage. Huiding may use cookies to log your IP address and to determine the path users take on our site and to identify repeat users of our site, but we do not link your IP address to your personal information. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so, if your browser permits. 

For specific purposes, in case you provide your name, gender, category and number of credentials, date of birth, country, title, occupation, contact details, services or information desired, customer code and other similar personal information that are required for registration or reading E-information by voluntarily filling in forms, you will be deemed having understood and accepted the use of your personal information and agreed that Huiding uses your personal information for the specific purposes. Use of Information Collected 

Huiding will not sell or rent your personal information at any time under any circumstance. Your personal information will only be used for Huiding business purposes such as, to meet your requests for certain products, documentation and/or services, to send solicited information, to process an order, to conduct a transaction, to handle a job application or to perform market research. Your personal information may be shared with other Huiding offices or subsidiaries around the world. 

However, Huiding may provide certain portion of your personal information to law executive organs and government authorities as so requested; and Huiding might disclose certain portion of your personal information within a strictly limited scope of recipients when Huiding reasonably thinks it is necessary for protecting Huiding, its customers or the public. You shall have foreseen and agreed to the occurrence of such events when you provide your personal information.
